Guide to the New Almaden Mine (Calif.) Collection, 1845-1973
Department of Special Collections
- SERIES VI: EMPLOYEE PAPERS, 1848-1945
  - PAYROLL RECORDS
    - Payroll deductions, New Almaden Stores, Incorporated, Mar.-Apr. 1922 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Payroll deductions, New Almaden Stores, Incorporated, May-Aug. 1922 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Payroll deductions, New Almaden Stores, Incorporated, Sept.-Oct. 1922 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Payroll deductions, New Almaden Stores, Incorporated, Nov.-Dec. 1922 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Payroll deductions, New Almaden Stores, Incorporated, Jan.-Mar. 1923 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Payroll deductions, New Almaden Stores, Incorporated, Apr.-May 1923 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Payroll deductions, New Almaden Stores, Incorporated, Aug.-Sept. 1923 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Payroll deductions, New Almaden Stores, Incorporated, Oct.-Dec. 1923 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Payroll deductions, New Almaden Stores, Incorporated, Jan.-Mar. 1924 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Payroll deductions, New Almaden Stores, Incorporated, Apr.-June 1924 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Payroll deductions, New Almaden Stores, Incorporated, July-Nov. 1924 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Wages, average daily, table, 1898-1899 (Folder Map Fol 95)
    - Wages, average daily, table, 1899-1900 (Folder Map Fol 95)
    - Wages, average daily, table, 1905-1906 (Folder Map Fol 95)
    - Wage comparisons, n.d. (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - TIME SHEETS
    - Time book, monthly, May 1883 [bound] (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Time book, monthly, 1904-1905 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Time book, monthly, 1906 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Time book, monthly, 1914-1915 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Time book, monthly, 1915 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Time book, monthly, 1915-1916 (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - Time book, monthly, 1915-1916 (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - Time book, monthly, 1915-1916 (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - Time book, monthly, 1915-1916 (Box 98, Folder 15)
    - Time book, monthly, 1915-1917 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Time book, monthly, 1916 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Time book, monthly, 1916 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Time book, monthly, 1916-1917 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Time book, monthly, 1916-1917 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Time book, monthly, 1917 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Time book, monthly, 1917-1919 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Time book, monthly, 1919 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Time book, monthly, 1940 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Time book, two-week period, 1941 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Time book, monthly, 1943 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Time book, monthly, 1945 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Time report, daily, 1917 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Time report, daily, 1919 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Time report, daily, Jan.June 1922 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Time report, daily, July-Sept. 1922 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Time report, daily, Oct.-Dec. 1922 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Time report, daily, Jan.-Mar. 1923 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Time report, daily, Apr.-June 1923 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Time report, daily, July-Sept. 1923 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Time report, daily, Oct.-Dec. 1923 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Time report, daily, Jan.-Mar. 1924 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Time report, daily, Apr.-June 1924 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Time report, daily, July-Sept. 1924 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Time report, daily, Oct.-Dec. 1924 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Time report, daily, Jan.-Apr. 1925 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Time report, daily, May-June 1925 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Time report, daily, July-Dec. 1925 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Time report, daily, 1926 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - MISCELLANEOUS
    - Account book of employee purchases, New Almaden Stores, 1848-1870 (Volume 62)
    - Applications for employment, 30 May 1940-19 June 1942 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Application assessments, 1940 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Autograph album, Carmen Castro, ca. 1886 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Contract bonds, 1891-1892 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Contracted laborers, list of names, 1 Feb. 1921 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Employee statistics; salary, marital status, 1918-1921 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Helping Hand Club, account book, 1906-1915 (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Helping Hand Club, Cookery for Working Men's Wives, 1890 (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Helping Hand Club, invoices, 1889-1893 (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - Infirmary poll-tax receipts, 1902 (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - Livestock, owned by employees, Iowana Farms, New Almaden Ranch, 1912-1919 (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - Manager's instructions to workers, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 16)
    - Miners, list of names, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 17)
    - Miner's Fund, accounts and invoices, 1885-1909 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Miner's Fund, coupon, n.d. (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Miner's Fund, deposit receipt, 1913 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Miner's Fund, infirmary poll tax record, 1902 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Miner's Fund, inventory, Aug. 1901 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Miner's Fund, loan receipts, 1888-1892 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Miner's Fund, minute book, 1896-1899 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Miner's Fund, physician notes, receipts, 1888-1912 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Miner's Fund, rules and regulations, 1883, 1917 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Nationality of employees, n.d. (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Naval contract, report on New Almaden Company Incorporated employees, 1918 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Newsclippings, reports, 1909 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Notice to workmen, 1909 (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - Occupation and residence logbook, n.d. (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - Selective Service, draft board classifications, 1943-1944 (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - School records, Hacienda district, report to school district trustees, 1886-1894 (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - School records, teacher's reports, 1890-1896 (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - School records, librarian's reports, 1889-1892 (Box 103, Folder 18)
    - School records, school census marshall's report, 1888-1896 (Box 103, Folder 19)
    - School records, orders, receipts, 1868-1879 (Box 103, Folder 20)
    - State poll tax receipts, 1902 (Box 103, Folder 21)
    - Union, Gold Hill, Nevada, by-laws, ca. 1866-1868 (Box 103, Folder 22)
    - Union, certificate of membership, ca. 1866-1868 (Box 103, Folder 23)
    - Union, stock certificate, ca. 1868 (Box 103, Folder 24)
- SERIES VII: MAPS AND PLANS
  - Coordinate listings, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Exhibit, list of materials sent, 1893 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Furnaces, sketches, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Plate descriptions, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Sketches, 188? (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Stations and pump works, 1877 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Topographical map of part of the property belonging to the Quicksilver Mining Company, 1887 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Tunnel plans, ca. 1874 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Tunnel plans, ca. 1927 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - OVERSIZE MAP BOOKS
    - Maps of the property of the Quicksilver Mining Company, 1 Jan. 1880
    - Maps of the property of the Quicksilver Mining Company, 1 Jan. 1880
    - Maps of the property of the Quicksilver Mining Company, 1 Jan. 1880
    - Atlas to accompany a monograph on the geology of the quicksilver deposits of the Pacific Slope, George F. Becker, 1887,Helping Hand Club, unbound, 4 copies
    - Map index, Hill office index of maps, old map guide based on organization found herein (Volume 63)
    - Tunnel plans, photographed, cut apart, and pasted together in Judges Law and Motion Calendar, Dept. 3, 1925-1926 (Volume 64)
  - BUILDINGS
    - Lodging house and Superintendent's residence, old #D12, 24.5x30 4 (Folder 1-1)
    - Boomerang, old #D13, 38.75 x 24.5 8/3, 1/3 (Folder 1-2)
    - Powder store for 700 kegs, old #D15, 1880; 17x19 4 (Folder 1-3)
      C.H.
    - Old powder houses, old #D16 & #346G, 1880; 8.5x9.5 (Folder 1-4)
      C. O'Brion
    - Quicksilver storeroom for 4,000 flasks, old #D17, 1880; 15x36 4 (Folder 1-5)
    - Quicksilver storeroom for 4,000 flasks, old #D18, 1880; 15.5 x 20.5 4,30 (Folder 1-6)
    - Office building, addition, old #D19, 1880; 23x33 4,8 (Folder 1-7)
    - Unidentified building, 26.5x28 2 (Folder 1-8)
    - Furnace #8, general arrangement, new condensers, ore bin, blueprint, 1917; 20x34.5 8 (Folder 1-9)
      Haas
    - Furnace #8, general arrangement, new condensers, ore bin, blueprint, 1917; 20x34.5 8 (Folder 1-10)
    - Truss mineral paint mill, sheet 2, 22.5x27 2 (Folder 1-11)
      Smith, Emery, and Company
    - Quicksilver furnace plant for for Senator mine, 1917; 29.5x38 16/3 (Folder 1-12)
    - Crusher foundations, 1942; 30x36 2 (Folder 1-13)
      C.M.
    - Sheave house, original, 1941; 29x41 1 (Folder 1-14)
    - Sheave house, original, 1941; 28.5x42 1 (Folder 1-15)
    - Sheave house, original, 1941; 28.5x42 1 (Folder 2-1)
    - Unidentified buildings, 24x30.5 (Folder 2-2)
    - Santa Rita shaft set, 1941; 17.5x23 (Folder 2-3)
    - Santa Rita shaft support, Juan Vega 300 station, 15x18 2 (Folder 2-4)
    - Bridge to Hacienda tunnel, boiler room sketch on verso, 14.5x53 4 (Folder 2-5)
    - Bridge to Santa Isabel planilla, 23x35 4 (Folder 2-6)
      Von Leicht
    - Shaft headframe, blueprint, 30.5x43 (Folder 2-7)
    - Plan of Kempville houses, 14x15 (Folder 2-8)
    - Santa Rita shaft cross head inner frame, 16x34.5 1/3 (Folder 2-9)
    - Garfield Gallows frame, old #B31, 1882; 31x41 4 (Folder 2-10)
      W.W. Bailey
    - Trestle track for conveying ore, old #D1, 1879; 19x24 4 (Folder 2-11)
    - Plan for roofs, old #D3, 29.5x38 8 (Folder 2-12)
      B.F. Graham
    - Plan of Hacienda greenhouse, old #349F, 1882; 11.5x31 8/3 (Folder 2-13)
      Ulrich
    - Headframe, old #350, 1942; 24.5x37 2 (Folder 2-14)
    - Santa Rita shaft structure plan and elevations, old #351, 1941; 34x44 4 (Folder 2-15)
    - Framework for condenser and dust chamber building, old #363, 21x42 (Folder 3-1)
    - Part of sheave house, old #366, 29x42 (Folder 3-2)
    - Plan for machine and blacksmith, shops, garage, trestles on verso, old #673, 42x50 (Folder 3-3)
    - Plan of buildings, dump, Garfield shaft, 1882; 22.5x50 20 (Folder 3-4)
    - Unidentified building, old #365, 1942; 29x36 (Folder 3-5)
      C.N.S.
    - Bridge, old #13A, 14x72 4,8 (Folder 3-6)
    - Layout of town, Helping Hand Hall, Chinese laundry, 9.75x12 (Folder 3-7)
    - Layout of buildings, 9.75x19.75 (Folder 3-8)
    - Building layout along creek, 8.5x11 (Folder 3-9)
    - Layout of buildings, matted, 21.25x23.5 (Folder 3-10)
      PLATS See Series List for description Plats located in folder 3
  - MACHINERY
    - Wooden flue water furnaces 1 and 2, A3, old #345, 1880; 12x58 3/16 (Folder 4-9)
      Healey
    - Pipeline under tanks to furnaces, A5, old #346, 1876; 20x56 30 (Folder 4-10)
      A.D. Foote
    - Pipeline profile, A4, old #347, 1876; 20x56 (Folder 4-11)
    - Cornish pump, working beam with bob and balance weight, copy, old #348, 8.5x11 (Folder 4-12)
    - Randol brake with weight for hoist, old #600, 11x21 1 (Folder 4-13)
    - Common standard fire door, blueprint, old #606, 1915; 19x23 1/2 (Folder 4-14)
    - Common standard oil regulator, 1917; 16x27.5 6 (Folder 4-15)
    - Common standard oil burner, 1916; 16x23 1/12 (Folder 5-1)
    - Common standard fire pan damper rigging, 1915; 16x22 1/2, 1/3, 1/6 (Folder 5-2)
      G.D.M., N.E.
    - Common standard damper regulator, 1913; 16x22 1/6 (Folder 5-3)
    - Common standard oil tank fittings, 1915; 19x23 1/3, 1/6 (Folder 5-4)
    - Common standard oil piping arrangement, 1915; 19x23.5 1 (Folder 5-5)
    - Common standard fire pan, 1915; 19x23.5 1/3, 1/6 (Folder 5-6)
    - Common standard oil heater, 1914; 19x23.5 (Folder 5-7)
    - Common standard oil burning arrangement, 1914; 19x23.5 (Folder 5-8)
    - Common standard oil piping arrangement and method of securing oil tank, 1915; 19x23.5 4/3 (Folder 5-9)
    - Hoisting compartment plans, Gray, Randol, Santa Isabel, old #606, 21x27 (Folder 5-10)
    - Pulley frame, Harry shaft, old #607, 1893; 21x44 8/3 (Folder 5-11)
    - Washing tanks for free mercury, old #608, 24x48 2 (Folder 5-12)
    - Plans for pump engine, Washington or Buena Vista, old #609, 1882; 27x41 1/3 (Folder 5-13)
      Prescott, Scott, and Company
    - Boxes for 16" x 60" double hoist, old #610, 1882; 21x27 1/6 (Folder 5-14)
    - Piston rod and pins for double hoist, 1882; 19x25 1/6 (Folder 5-15)
    - Crank shaft and pins for double hoist, 1882; 20x30 1/3 (Folder 6-1)
    - Camshafts, 1882; 17x27.5 1/12 (Folder 6-2)
      Prescott, Scott, abd Company
    - Clutch shafts, 1882; 21.5x29 1/3 (Folder 6-3)
    - Brake gear, old #610, 1882; 27.5 x 2/3 (Folder 6-4)
    - Steam chest covers, 1882; 19.5x30 1/12 (Folder 6-5)
    - Brake apparatus, 1882; 24x30 1/3 (Folder 6-6)
    - Valve bracket, 1882; 23x29 1/6 (Folder 6-7)
    - Pumping engine, Harry, old #611, 1893; 25.5 x 2 (Folder 6-8)
      Harrower
    - Self dumping skip with annotations, old #613, 1883; 22x36 2 (Folder 6-9)
    - Pump station, Buena Vista 2300, old #614, 1892; 23x28 2 (Folder 6-10)
    - Plan of steam and air pipes, Buena Vista shaft, approved Randol, old #615, 1882; 27.5x42 4 (Folder 6-11)
    - Plan of steam and air pipes, for 2 boilers, Buena Vista, old #617, 1882; 23x34 4 (Folder 6-12)
    - New Almaden direct acting engine, O'Neill's valve, old #6201, 1882; 29.5x52 2/3 (Folder 6-13)
    - New Almaden direct acting engine, starting bars and pins, old #6202, 1882; 22x29 1/6 (Folder 6-14)
    - New Almaden direct acting engine, Platform and Steps, old #6203, 1882; 29.5x46 2/3 (Folder 6-15)
    - New Almaden direct acting engine, initial and exp. cylinder piston rod, old #6204, 1882; 18x25 1/3 (Folder 7-1)
    - New Almaden direct acting engine, initial and exp. cul. exhaust and steam valve stems old #6205, 1882; 20x30 1/12 (Folder 7-2)
    - Throttle valve, old #6206, 1882; 20x27 1/12 (Folder 7-3)
    - Initial cylinder rocker shaft connect, old #6207, 1882; 22x28 1/12 (Folder 7-4)
    - Initial exp. cyl. stuffing box old #6208, 1882; 24x33 1/3 (Folder 7-5)
    - Relief valve for initial cylinder, old #620g., 1882; 21x29 1/12 (Folder 7-6)
    - Initial cylinder piston, old #62010, 1882; 24x28.5 1/6 (Folder 7-7)
    - Initial cylinder piston, lower bracket, old #62011, 1882; 26x24.5 1/6 (Folder 7-8)
    - Steps for engine baseplate. old #62012, 1882; 27x37 1/12 (Folder 7-9)
    - Cut off eccentric rod, old #62013, 1882; 26.5x36.5 1/12 (Folder 7-10)
    - Posts for platform, old #62014, 1882; 24x27 1/12 (Folder 7-11)
    - Piston for expansion cylinder. old #62015, 1882; 26x37 1/6 (Folder 7-12)
    - Crank shaft, outboard pillow, block and sole plate, old #62016, 1882; 28x46 1/3 (Folder 7-13)
    - Special endless belt ore feeder blueprint, old #624, 1914; 16x21 1, 1/3, 2/3 (Folder 7-14)
      Bolton
    - Design for lower ropeway terminal, blueprint, old #625, 1890; 19x28 16/3 (Folder 7-15)
      Vulcan
    - Plan of pitwork, old #627, 23x44 2 (Folder 8-1)
    - Initial cylinder links, old #628, 1882; 27.5x29.5 1/6 (Folder 8-2)
    - Design for upper ropeway terminal and selfload, old #630., 1890?; 20x25 4 (Folder 8-3)
    - New Ardilla sink, arrangement of engines, bins, sheave, old #631, 1899; 19x25 4 (Folder 8-4)
      C.C. Derby
    - Mineral plant mill, old #650, 20.5x30 8 (Folder 8-5)
      Smith, Emery
    - General arrangement, #8 furnace, ore bin, etc., blueprint, old #653, 1917; 19.5x35 8 (Folder 8-6)
    - Senator headframe, ore pocket on verso, old #655, 28x36 (Folder 8-7)
    - Western precipitation Company, Los Angeles, 8 pieces, old #661, 1916; 24x35 (Folder 8-8)
      C.R.F.P.
    - Wheel hardy gurdy, old #B-1, #668, 14x17 2 (Folder 8-9)
    - Foundation of pumping engine, old #674, 1882; 30x45 4 (Folder 8-10)
    - Winding drum for hoist, old #B-13, 1879; 22x28.5 2/3 (Folder 8-11)
    - Air compressor covering, 1969; 18.5x24 1/2 (Folder 8-12)
      RKL
    - Iron car body of wooden truck, old #B20, 12.5x15.5 (Folder 8-13)
    - Cross head landing, 15x26 1/6 (Folder 8-14)
    - Gallows frame for Buena Vista shaft, old #B30, 1882; 31x49 4 (Folder 8-15)
    - Santa Rita Shaft fire doors, 10x14 1 (Folder 9-1)
    - Direct acting engine, 1882; 29.5x49 2/3 (Folder 9-2)
      Prescott, Scott, and Co.
    - Direct acting engine, Cylinder heads, 1882; 24x30 1/3 (Folder 9-3)
    - Direct acting engine, eccentrics made of cast iron, 1882; 25.5x28.75 1/6 (Folder 9-4)
    - Direct acting engine, connecting rod, 1882; 28x39 1/6 (Folder 9-5)
    - Direct acting engine, column to support platform, 1882; 15x29 1/6 (Folder 9-6)
    - Direct acting engine, valve condenser, 1882; 6.25x36.25 1/6 (Folder 9-7)
    - Direct acting engine, valve condenser, 1882; 23x26 1/3 (Folder 9-8)
    - Direct acting engine, valve condenser, 1882; 22.5x26.5 1/6 (Folder 9-9)
    - Direct acting engine, valve condenser, 1882; 20x25.25 1/12 (Folder 9-10)
    - Direct acting engine, column with gauges, 1882; 23x29 1/3 (Folder 9-11)
    - Direct acting engine, column with gauges, 1882; 25.5x28.25 2/3 (Folder 9-12)
    - Direct acting engine, column with gauges, 1882; 18.25x34 1/12 (Folder 9-13)
    - Direct acting engine, column with gauges, 1882; 29.5x56 1/12 (Folder 9-14)
    - Direct acting engine, column with gauges, 1882; 27.5x40 2/3 (Folder 9-15)
    - Direct acting engine, column with gauges, 1882; 23.5x30.5 1/3 (Folder 10-1)
    - Direct acting engine, column with gauges, 1882; 24x29.5 1 (Folder 10-2)
    - Direct acting engine, column with gauges, 1882; 23.5x30.5 2/3 (Folder 10-3)
      Prescott, Scott, and Co., W.W. Bailey
    - Direct acting engine, column with gauges, 1882; 25x32 1/2 (Folder 10-4)
    - Direct acting engine, column with gauges, 1882; 26x36 1 (Folder 10-5)
    - Direct acting engine, column with gauges, 1882; 23x29.5 1 (Folder 10-6)
    - Direct acting engine, column with gauges, 1882; 21.25x28.5 1 (Folder 10-7)
    - Direct acting engine, column with gauges, 1882; 25.5x29.5 1 (Folder 10-8)
    - Direct acting engine, column with gauges, 1882; 21.5x34 1 (Folder 10-9)
    - Direct acting engine, column with gauges, 1882; 24x29.5 1/3 (Folder 10-10)
    - Direct acting engine, initial cylinder cam shaft connections, 1882; 18.25x27.5 1 (Folder 10-11)
    - Direct acting engine, connecting rod for cold water pump, 1882; 10.5x21.5 (Folder 10-12)
    - Car wheel, hyatt bearing, ca.1922; 14x18 (Folder 10-13)
    - Iron ore screen, color, 11.5x34 2/3 (Folder 10-14)
    - Machinery, figures 1-9, 2 pcs, 8.5x15 (Folder 10-15)
    - Plan for Gallows, center of shaft, center of gallows frame, 8x13 (Folder 11-1)
    - Flywheel, 24 ft., 1882; 25x37 1 (Folder 11-2)
    - Wagon, old #B19, 15.5x27.5 2/3 (Folder 11-3)
    - Upper pressure tank, section 9, 6.5x8 (Folder 11-4)
  - ORE BINS
    - Graph calendar schedule for completion of mill components, December-March, 24x32 (Folder 11-5)
    - Proposed 100 TPD Gould Rotary Furnace site topo map, Nov., 1969; 23x24 10 (Folder 11-6)
      VVB, KGH
    - Proposed 100 TPD Gould Rotary Furnace site topo map, Nov., 1969; 21.5x22.5 10 (Folder 11-7)
    - Proposed 100 TPD Gould Rotary Furnace site topo map, Nov., 1969; 23x24 10 (Folder 11-8)
    - Feeder pier base form, 14x24 2 (Folder 11-9)
    - Mill plan, December, 1969; 16x24 10 (Folder 11-10)
      SWV
    - Profile northerly pier and fine ore bin, 9x12 10 (Folder 11-11)
    - Profile northerly pier and fine ore bin, 1969; 19x24 10 (Folder 11-12)
      VVB
    - Topographic profile along proposed centerline of 100 TPD rotary furnace, 1969; 15x22 10 (Folder 11-13)
    - Fine ore bin and lower/upper ride ring, 8.5x15 (Folder 11-14)
    - Mill profile from fine ore to burnt ore bin, 15.5x23 (Folder 11-15)
    - Profile of proposed center line of new 100 ton furnace, September, 1969; 24x46 5 (Folder 12-1)
    - Projected position dust chamber/combustion chamber, 24x53 (Folder 12-2)
    - Mill structure, April, 1970; 9x24 10 (Folder 12-3)
      S. Verhaart
    - Feeder pier, upper form, 14x24 2 (Folder 12-4)
    - Draft of 100 TPD Rotary Furnace site, topographic map, 24x40 (Folder 12-5)
    - Ore Bin headframes, 1941; 26x28.75 (Folder 12-6)
    - Ore Bin headframes, 1941; 26x42 1 (Folder 12-7)
    - Ore Bin headframes, original, 1941; 26x42 1 (Folder 12-8)
    - Plan of ore bins at foot of incline, section through cross section, old #D10, 1879; 31x48 8/3 (Folder 12-9)
    - Plan of ore bins at foot of incline, section through cross section, old #D9/672, 1879; 31x48 8/3 (Folder 12-10)
    - End elevation of ore bins, old #D8, 1879; 19x22.5 8/3 (Folder 12-11)
    - Side elevations of ore bins, old #D6, 1879; 22x38 8/3 (Folder 12-12)
    - Side elevation section through AA, old #D5, 1879; 23x41 8/3 (Folder 12-13)
    - Tramway to ore bin, 1942; 21x25 1 (Folder 12-14)
      C.N. Schuette
    - 800 level pocket, Santa Rita Shaft, 1942; 34x44 4 (Folder 12-15)
    - Proposed Cableway, Mine Hill dump to mill, old #659, 22x33.5 20 (Folder 13-1)
    - unidentified section of mill structure, 12x24 10 (Folder 13-2)
    - Crusher foundations, 1942; 32.25 x 36 2 (Folder 13-3)
    - Ore bins, 34x55 2 (Folder 13-4)
    - Ore bins, 1942; 24x36 2 (Folder 13-5)
    - Ore bins, 34x55 (Folder 13-6)
    - Loading platform, 32x42 2 (Folder 13-7)
    - Alterations to ore bins to receive crushing machinery, blueprint, old #621, 1916; 28x40 8/3 (Folder 13-8)
      W.H. Landers, Esq.
  - FURNACES
    - Guibal fan, 8 diameter, old #B4, 1881; 19 x 28.75 2/3 (Folder 13-9)
    - Guibal fan, 8 diameter, old #B5, 1883; 20x20 2 (Folder 13-10)
    - Guibal fan, 8 diameter, old #B6, 1881; 20.75x27.5 2 (Folder 13-11)
      Wagoner
    - Guibal fan, 8 diameter, details, detail of nozzle on verso, old #B7, 16.5x36 1 (Folder 13-12)
    - Sketch for installation of roots blower of screen for condensing apparatus, purification tank on verso, old #B8, 1880; 24x36 2 (Folder 13-13)
      JBR
    - Downcast by Martin White Co., Plate D, old #B11, 9.5 x 12.5 (Folder 13-14)
      Martin White Company
    - Soot kettle, old #B14, 1878; 17x29 3 (Folder 13-15)
    - Wagoner's soot worker, letter attached from Wagoner and Hammond, old #B15, 1882; 8.5x11 2/3 (Folder 14-1)
    - Soot pan, old #B17, 1881; 12x19.5 (Folder 14-2)
    - Soot pan, old #B18, 10x10.5 (Folder 14-3)
      C. Gyurkovitz
    - Plans for hopper discharge, old #B22 & #667, 8x10 (Folder 14-4)
    - Purification of smoke, old #B23, 1880; 20x36 16/3, 4/3 (Folder 14-5)
    - Trompe nozzle on discharge pipe, old #C4, 1879; 12.75 x 27 14 th (Folder 14-6)
    - Trompe nozzle on discharge pipe, old #C5, 1879; 13x27 14 th (Folder 14-7)
    - Trompe, old #C6, 31x38 4 (Folder 14-8)
    - Trompe pipes, old #C7, 1879; 15.5 x 32.5 2/3 (Folder 14-9)
    - Trompe, old #C9, 14.5x28 4 (Folder 14-10)
    - Damper to smoke stack, old #C10, 1879; 10.75 x 18.75 2/3 (Folder 14-11)
    - Baker flue, old #C11, 9.75 x 15 (Folder 14-12)
    - Tank for water elevator, old #C12, 1879; 23x25 3 (Folder 14-13)
    - Water tank for elevator, old #C13, 1880; 13.5 x 19.5 2/3, 2 (Folder 14-14)
    - Settling tank, furnace #9, old #C16 & #660, 1880; 12x13 2 (Folder 14-15)
      CH
    - Water level equalizer, old #C18, 13.5 x 21.25 3 (Folder 15-1)
    - Elevator behind furnace #3, old #C19, 28x49 (Folder 15-2)
    - Elevator behind furnace #3, old #C21, 30x52 (Folder 15-3)
    - Cage for hydraulic water elevator, Old #C22, 26.5x38 2,4, 2/3 (Folder 15-4)
    - 12 1/2 hydraulic ram elevator, California machine works, old #C24, 26x37 2/3 (Folder 15-5)
    - Hydraulic elevator for furnace #3, old #C27, 1879; 23.5x37 4/3, 2/3 (Folder 15-6)
    - Hydraulic elevator for furnace #3, color, old #C28, 24.5x39 4/3, 2/3 (Folder 15-7)
    - Hydraulic elevator for furnace #2, old #C29 & #664, 1879; 39x46.5 2 (Folder 15-8)
    - Water tank elevator for furnaces #1 & #2, old #C31 & #663, 24.75 x 41.25 3 (Folder 15-9)
    - Ground plan of track from new ore bin, old #D2 & #358, 31x39 2/3, 4 (Folder 15-10)
    - End elevation of ore bins, old #D7, 1879; 20x22 8/3 (Folder 15-11)